Guide to the Reynolds Price Papers, 1927-2010 and undated, bulk 1956-2006
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Correspondence Series (RESTRICTED), 1936-2004 and undated, (64 boxes)
  - Authors' Correspondence Subseries (RESTRICTED), 1940-2004 and undated, (8 boxes)
    - K-P 1959-2003 and undated, (31 folders) ENTIRE BOX IS RESTRICTED. (Box AC4)
      - Meredith, William, 1970-1979, (14 items)
      - Mitchell, Julian, 1959-1988 and undated, (48 items)
      - Morgan, Robert, 2000-2003 and undated, (3 items)
      - Morris, Willie, 1997, (1 item)
      - Morrison, Toni, 1974-1992 and undated, (10 items)
      - Naumoff, Lawrence, 1972-2000, (30 items)
      - Nelson, Betty Palmer, 1992, (1 item)
      - Oates, Joyce Carol, 1976-1983, (5 items)
      - O'Brien, Edna, 1962, (1 item)
      - Owen, Guy, 1974-1976, (6 items)
      - Parker, Dorothy, 1961, (1 item)
      - Patton, Frances Gray, 1960-1977, (3 items)
      - Payne, Peggy, 1994, (1 item)
      - Pearson, T. R., 1986, (1 item)
      - Percy, Walker, 1966-1992, (9 items)
      - Porter, Joe, 1980-2001, (54 items)
    - P-S, 1956-2003 and undated, (20 folders) ENTIRE BOX IS RESTRICTED. (Box AC5)
      - Price, Leontyne, 1975-1983 and undated, (8 items)
      - Ransom, John Crowe, 1987, (1 item)
      - Rorem, Ned, 1997-2003, (6 items)
      - Rubin, Louis, 1965-1997, (14 items)
      - Salinger, Wendy, 1997, (1 item)
      - Schiff, James, 1994-2002, (40 items)
      - Seay, Jim, 1973-1990, (3 items)
      - Sendak, Maurice, 1999, (1 item)
      - Settle, Mary Lee, 1978-1982, (7 items)
      - Shivers, Louise, 1976-1986 and undated, (20 items)
      - Smith, Charlie, 1969-1989 and undated, (43 items)
      - Smith, Dave, 1988-2000 and undated`, (28 items)
      - Smith, Lee, 1969-1998, (16 items)
      - Snyder, Gary, 1974-1977, (4 items)
      - Sondheim, Stephen, 1997, (1 item)
      - Spencer, Elizabeth, 1987-2002, (17 items)
      - Spender, Stephen, 1956-1957 Mar., (49 items)
    - S-U, 1956-2003 and undated, (18 folders) ENTIRE BOX IS RESTRICTED. (Box AC6)
      - Spender, Stephen, 1957 Apr.-1999 and undated, (289 items)
      - Steele, Max, 1967-1988 and undated, (22 items)
      - Styron, William, 1956-1994, (31 items)
      - Tan, Amy, 1995, (1 item)
      - Tate, Allen, 1966-1975, (6 items)
      - Taylor, James, 2001, (2 items)
      - Tyler, Anne, 1960-2003 and undated, (36 items)
      - Updike, John, 1962-2000 and undated, (8 items)
    - V-W, 1940-2001 and undated, (13 folders) ENTIRE BOX IS RESTRICTED. (Box AC7)
      - Verdelle, A. J., 1996, (2 items)
      - Voll, Daniel, 1992-2001 and undated, (39 items)
      - Vonnegut, Kurt, 1997, (1 item)
      - Wallace, Randall, 1971-1986, (13 items)
      - Warren, Robert Penn, 1980, (1 item)
      - Welty, Eudora, 1940-1994 and undated, (225 items)
      - Williams, Jonathan, 1969-1984, (51 items)
    - American Academy of Arts and Letters, 1993-2004 and undated, (9 folders) ENTIRE BOX IS RESTRICTED. (Box AC8)
- Writings Series (RESTRICTED), 1935-2004 and undated, (92 boxes)
  ENTIRE SERIES IS RESTRICTED. See individual subseries notes for specific restrictions.
  The Writings Series is divided into the Writings by Price Subseries and the Writings by Others Subseries.
  - Writings by Price Subseries (RESTRICTED), 1946-2003 and undated, (76 boxes)
    Chiefly manuscripts, typescripts, and proofs of novels, short stories, poetry, plays, and a variety of nonfiction books by Reynolds Price. Overall arrangement of the subseries is chronological, with some exceptions.
    The majority of Price's published books and plays (minus some small press publications and limited editions) appear in order of publication date in boxes WP1-WP70. For each book, materials are then arranged in order of their writing and editing history. In cases of approximate or inferred dates, strict chronological order is occasionally ignored, with the main sequence of writing and editing the text--as reflected in notes, manuscripts, typescripts, and proofs--being favored over such later matters in the publication process as jacket copy, ads, and adaptations into other genres and media (such as screenplays and audiobooks).
    Materials for individual short works appear in the last six boxes of the subseries, WP71-WP77, in four categories: uncollected poems, uncollected stories, uncollected nonfiction, and student work. The first three of these groups are arranged alphabetically by title; Price's student work, from high school through his years at Oxford, is arranged chronologically.
    [RESTRICTED: materials in this subseries are open for researchers to view but not to duplicate. During Price's lifetime and twenty years thereafter, duplication by any means of materials in this subseries requires prior written permission from him or his literary executors.]
    - A Long and Happy Life (novel, 1962) RESTRICTED (Box WP1)
      - Notes, 1957, (2 folders)
      - Partial Fair Copy, 1958-1959
      - Notes and drafts, 1958-1960, (5 folders)
      - Notes and drafts, 1960, (5 folders)
      - Typescript, 1961 and undated, (Folders 1-6 of 7)
      - Typescript, 1961 and undated, (Folder 7 of 7) (Box WP2)
      - Typescript with charts and windows specifications for printer, 1961, (4 folders)
      - Typescripts with Harry Ford's specifications for printer, 1961, (4 folders)
      - Plate proof: Corrected pages, 1961
      - Proofs, 1961-1964, (3 folders)
      - Screenplays by Price and other authors
        - Charles Eastman, 1964 Sept. 5, (2 folders)
        - Notes and first draft by Price for Jack Garfein, 1965, (2 folders)
        - Draft by Price as presented to Jack Garfein, 1965 Apr., (2 folders)
        - Drafts by Price and Garfein, 1965-1966, (Folder 1 of 3)
        - Drafts by Price and Garfein, 1965-1966, (Folders 2-3 of 3) (Box WP3)
        - Fair copy by Price and Garfein, 1966, (2 folders)
        - Draft with revisions by Price, ca. 1969, (2 folders)
        - Fair copy of 1969 revisions, circa 1969
        - Notes by Price and Richard Neubert, 1970 June-July
        - Draft by Price and Richard Neubert with revisions by both, 1970 June-July, (2 folders)
        - Draft with notes and revisions by Richard Neubert, 1970, (2 folders)
        - Draft with revisions by Price and Richard Neubert, 1970., (2 folders)
      - Miscellaneous, 1961-1971 and undated
      - Play prepared by John Clum from RP's screenplay for Duke Summer Theater, 1976
      - Typescript of Clum adaptation, signed by Price and notated for staging, circa 1976
      - Draft of screenplay by Stephanie Keys, 1988
      - Typescript of screenplay by Beth Henley, 1989, Mar. (Box WP4)
      - Dedication page, undated
      - Encounter proof of Part One, undated
      - Jacket sketch and jacket, by Harry Ford, undated
      - Samples of paperback cover, undated
      - Notes and drafts, undated
    - The Names and Faces of Heroes (short stories, 1963) RESTRICTED (Box WP4)
      Note: see also "Correspondence and application materials for Guggenheim Foundation, 1960-1970" under "Uncollected fiction" in Box WP69 for other early manuscripts of individual stories later collected in The Names and Faces of Heroes.
      - Possible titles, undated
      - Proof from which Price read at YMHA, New York, 1963 Mar.
      - Draft of introduction to reading, undated
      - Program of reading, undated
      - Harry Ford's specifications for English edition, 1963
      - A Chain of Love, notes and drafts, 1955 and undated, (3 folders)
      - A Chain of Love, typed draft, undated
      - A Chain of Love, proof (as set, but never published, by Paris Review, 1957)
      - A Chain of Love, drafts and revisions, 1962
      - A Chain of Love, typescript with revisions, undated
      - A Chain of Love, abridged from The Names and Faces of Heroes, undated
      - The Warrior Princess Ozimba, notes and drafts, 1956-1961 and undated
      - Michael Egerton, 1951-1954 and undated
      - The Anniversary, notes and drafts, 1955-1958, (2 folders)
      - The Anniversary, typescript, undated
      - Uncle Grant, notes and drafts and proof from Encounter, 1961 and undated
      - Uncle Grant, manuscript fragments, 1961-1962
      - Uncle Grant, typescript fragments, undated
      - Printer's typescript, prepared by Harry Ford and copy editor, 1963, (2 folders) (Box WP5)
      - Plate proof, 1963, (2 folders)
      - Jacket proof, 1963
      - Sample proof, 1963, Feb.
      - Proofs, 1963, (2 folders)
    - A Generous Man (novel, 1966) RESTRICTED (Box WP5)
      - Notes, 1964-1965 and undated
      - First draft, 1964-1965, (5 folders)
      - Typescript, undated, (4 folders)
      - Typescript with Price's changes while book was in press, undated, (Folders 1-2 of 4)
      - Typescript with Price's changes while book was in press, undated, (Folders 3-4 of 4) (Box WP6)
      - Printer's copy with Harry Ford's specifications, 1966, (4 folders)
      - Plate proof, 1966, (4 folders)
      - Proofs, 1966, (4 folders)
      - Synopsis for Columbia Pictures Corporation, 1966 Feb.
      - French proof, 1970, (2 folders)
      - Jacket proofs: Atheneum and Signet, undated
    - Love and Work (novel, 1968) RESTRICTED (Box WP6)
      - Notes, 1965-1968 and undated
      - First draft, 1967, (2 folders)
      - Price's typescript with revisions, 1968, (2 folders)
      - Final typescript with revisions by Price (made while book was in press), undated, (Folder 1 of 2)
      - Final typescript with revisions by Price (made while book was in press), undated, (Folder 2 of 2) (Box WP7)
      - Printer's copy with Harry Ford's specifications, 1968, (3 folders)
      - Plate proofs, 1968, (2 folders)
      - Proofs, 1968, (2 folders)
      - Sample covers and jacket proof, undated
      - Jacket copy, undated
    - Permanent Errors (short stories and novella, 1970) RESTRICTED (Box WP7)
      - Notes, 1967-1969 and undated
      - To the Reader, draft and typescript, 1970 and undated
      - The Happiness of Others, drafts, 1967 and undated
      - A Dog's Death, drafts, 1966-1967 and undated
      - Scars, notes and drafts, 1967 and undated
      - Waiting at Dachau, notes, drafts, and Esquire proofs, 1968-1969 and undated
      - Late Warnings, notes and drafts, 1966-1968 and undated
      - Invitation for Jesse Rehder, drafts, 1967 and undated
      - Summer Games, drafts, 1963 and undated
      - Truth and Lies, drafts, 1963 and undated
      - Good and Bad Dreams, notes, drafts, and Playboy uncorrected proof, 1963-1970 and undated
      - Walking Lessons, notes and drafts, 1969-1970 and undated, (2 folders)
      - To the Reader, typescript, undated
      - The Happiness of Others, typescript, undated
      - A Dog's Death, typescript, undated
      - Scars, typescript, undated
      - Waiting at Dachau, typescript, undated (Box WP8)
      - Late Warnings, typescript, undated
      - Invitation for Jessie Rehder, typescript, undated
      - Summer Games, typescript, undated
      - Truth and Lies, typescript, undated
      - Good and Bad Dreams, typescript, undated
      - Walking Lessons, typescript, undated, (2 folders)
      - Typescript with Price's changes made while book was in press, undated, (5 folders)
      - Printer's copy with Harry Ford's specifications, 1970, (4 folders)
      - Plate proof, 1970, (4 folders)
      - Page proof, 1970 (Box WP9)
      - Proofs, 1970, (4 folders)
      - Jacket copy, undated
      - Jacket proof, sample covers, and Harry Ford's specifications, undated
      - Paperback cover, undated
      - Miscellaneous, 1970-1982 and undated
    - Things Themselves (essays, 1972) RESTRICTED (Box WP9)
      - To the Reader, notes and drafts, 1970-1971 and undated
      - Dodging Apples, drafts, 1963-1971 and undated
      - Five Sketches for a Screenplay, drafts, undated
      - News for the Mineshaft, notes and drafts, 1967 and undated
      - Pylon - The Posture of Worship, notes and drafts, 1968 and undated
      - A Reasonable Guide Through Perilous Seas, draft, undated
      - The Onlooker, Smiling, notes and drafts, 1969-1972 and undated
      - Frightening Gift, first draft, 1970
      - The Wings of a Dove - A Single Combat, notes and draft, 1971 and undated
      - Dodo, Phoenix, or Tough Old Cock? notes and draft, 1971 and undated
      - For Ernest Hemingway, notes and draft, 1971 and undated, (3 folders)
      - Four Abrahams, Four Isaacs by Rembrandt, notes and drafts, 1971 and undated (Box WP10)
      - Poem Doctrinal and Exemplary to a Nation, drafts, 1971 and undated
      - Typescript with Price's revisions, undated, (2 folders)
      - Printer's copy with Harry Ford's specifications, 1972, (2 folders)
      - Plate proof, 1972, (3 folders)
      - Proofs, 1972, (4 folders)
      - Jacket proof and sample covers, 1972
    - Presence and Absence (translations, 1973) RESTRICTED (Box WP10)
      - Original corrected manuscript, 1972
      - Original typed manuscript, 1972
      - Printer's proof, 1972-1973
      - Author's corrected galley proof, 1973
    - The Surface of Earth (novel, 1975) RESTRICTED (Box WP10)
      - Notes and schedules, 1973-1974 and undated
      - First draft, Book One, 1972-1973, (Folder 1 of 2)
      - First draft, Book One, 1972-1973, (Folder 2 of 2) (Box WP11)
      - First draft, Book Two, 1973-1974, (2 folders)
      - First draft, Book Three, 1974, (2 folders)
      - Author's note, manuscripts and transcript, 1974-1975
      - Price's typescript with revisions, undated, (Folders 1-5 of 6)
      - Price's typescript with revisions, undated, (Folder 6 of 6) (Box WP12)
      - Printer's copy with Harry Ford's specifications, 1975, (5 folders)
      - Printer's copy with Harry Ford's specifications, 1975 (cont.)
      - Honest Hearts, typescript draft for Esquire with suggested corrections by Gordon Lish, undated
      - Galley proofs for Esquire, 1973
      - Proofs, 1975, (7 folders)
      - Jacket copy, 1974 and undated
      - Cover photographs, 1976 and undated
      - Jacket proofs, undated
      - Paperback cover, undated
      - Sample pages with Price's notes, changes for Atheneum paperback edition, 1981-1983, (2 folders)
      - Photograph, undated
    - Early Dark (play, 1977) RESTRICTED (Box WP13)
      - Manuscript I (notebook), 1976 July-Aug.
      - Manuscript II (notebook), 1976 July-Aug.
      - Final transcript, 1976
      - Printer's copy with Harry Ford's specifications, 1977
      - Typescript drafts of preface, 1976 and undated
      - Sample pages, 1977 Jan.
      - Proofs, 1977, (3 folders)
      - Miscellany, undated
    - A Palpable God (translations and essay, 1978) RESTRICTED (Box WP13)
      - Notes, 1975-1976 and undated
      - A notebook of translations, 1975-1976
      - Drafts: Preface; Note on Translating and Selection, and the texts, 1976 and undated, (6 folders)
      - Preface to Mark, four manuscript and typescript drafts, 1976 July and undated
      - The Good News According to Mark, proof, 1976
      - Preface with introduction and changes for presentation as lectures at Salzburg seminar, Austria, 1977 June.
      - Page proof with author's corrections, 1977
      - Printer's copy, typed by Price, with Harry Ford's specifications, 1978, (8 folders)
      - Proofs, 1978, (4 folders)
      - To the Reader, five manuscript and typescript drafts, 1979 Apr. and undated
      - Three typescript fragments of To the Reader and translated texts, undated, (Folder 1 of 3)
      - Three typescript fragments of To the Reader and translated texts, undated, (Folders 2-3 of 3) (Box WP14)
    - Nine Mysteries (poetry, 1979) RESTRICTED (Box WP14)
      - Nine Mysteries, 1979, undated
      - Miscellaneous
      - Typescript drafts and Fragments, 1979
      - First, Second and Third proofs, 1979
      - First printing and Sample pages, 1979
      - Miscellaneous proofs
      - Annunciation, draft, undated
      - Ascension, draft, undated
      - Dead Girl, undated
      - Naked Boy, draft, 1977 and undated
      - Reparation, drafts, 1977
      - Resurrection, draft, undated
      - Nine Mysteries typescript, undated
      - Nine Mysteries cover, undated
    - The Source of Light (novel, 1981) RESTRICTED (Box WP14)
      - Notes and fragments, 1971-1980
      - First draft, 1978, (7 folders)
      - First draft, typed, undated (Box WP15)
      - Typescript
      - Printer's copy, typed by Price, with Harry Ford's specifications, 1981, (8 folders)
      - Proofs, 1981, (5 folders)
      - Back cover copy for paperback edition, 1985 Jan.
      - Paperback covers, undated
      - Proof of binding, undated
      - Manuscript log, undated
      - Author's questionnaire, 1980 Sept.
    - Vital Provisions (poetry, 1982) RESTRICTED (Box WP15)
      - The Alchemist, manuscripts and typescript, 1970 and undated
      - Angel, manuscripts and typescripts, 1965, 1981 and undated
      - Anniversary, typescript, undated
      - The Annual Heron, typescript, undated
      - Annunciation, manuscript, typescript, and proof, 1975
      - At the Gulf, manuscripts and typescripts, 1970 and undated
      - At the Gulf, galley proof, 1977
      - Attis, manuscript, typescripts, and proof, 1970, 1983 and undated
      - Aurora, typescript, 1982
      - Black Water, typescript, undated
      - Christ Child's Song at the End of Night, typescript, 1978
      - Cumaean Song, typescript, undated
      - Dead Girl (Mark 5), typescript and proof, undated
      - Divine Propositions, typescript, undated
      - The Dream of a House, manuscripts and typescripts, 1977 and undated
      - The Dream of Food, typescripts, 1980 and undated
      - The Dream of Lee, typescripts, undated
      - "For Leontyne Price After Ariadne," manuscripts, typescripts, and proof, 1973, 1979 and undated
      - Found, For My Brother, typescript, 1981
      - I say of any man, typescripts and proof, 1961 and undated
      - Instruction (Matthew 27:5), typescripts, undated
      - Man and Faun, manuscripts, typescripts, 1966-1967 and undated
      - Memoranda, typescripts, 1982
      - Night Speech, typescript, undated
      - Pictures of the Dead, typescripts, undated
      - Pure Boys and Girls, typescripts and proof, 1978 and undated, (2 folders)
      - Questions for a Student (A.M., 18 March 1969), typescripts, 1975 and undated
      - A Rainbow and a Day-Old Calf, typescript, undated
      - Seafarer, typescripts, 1979 and undated
      - Sleeping Wife (Matthew 27:19), typescripts, 1973
      - Ten Years, Four Days, typescript, undated
      - To My Niece--Our Photograph in a Hammock, manuscripts and typescript, 1970 and undated
      - Torso of an Archaic Apollo, draft, typescript, 1968-1969 and undated
      - Your Element, typescript, undated (Box WP16)
      - Fair copy, revised, 1981 (2 vols.)
      - Drafts, undated, (Folder 1 of 2)
      - Drafts, undated, (Folder 2 of 2)
      - Table of Contents, preface, miscellany (drafts), 1982 and undated
      - Typescript (incomplete), undated
      - Proof, unbound, 1982, (2 folders)
      - Proof, bound, 1982
      - Page proof, 1982
      - Author's questionnaire, 1982 Feb.
    - Mustian (novels and short story, 1983) RESTRICTED (Box WP16)
      - Preface, manuscript and typescript drafts, 1982 Nov.
      - Proofs with Price's corrections, 1983, (Folder 1 of 2)
      - Proofs with Price's corrections, 1983, (Folder 2 of 2) (Box WP17)
      - Advertisements and proofs, 1983-1984 and undated
      - Covers, undated
      - Front flap copy draft, undated
    - Private Contentment (play, 1984) RESTRICTED (Box WP17)
      - Notes, 1981 March-May
      - First draft, 1981
      - Typed draft, 1981
      - Shooting script for PBS American Playhouse, 1982 Jan.
      - Printer's copy with Harry Ford's specifications, 1984
      - First proof with Price's corrections, fragments, 1984
      - Proof, 1984
      - Stage plan for Private Contentment, 1985
      - Cover photograph, undated
    - Kate Vaiden (novel, 1986) RESTRICTED (Box WP17)
      - Handwritten draft, 1983-1985, (2 folders)
      - First corrected printout, superceded 1984 Mar.
      - Notes, 1985-1985 and undated
      - Partial typescript with changes, 1985, (2 folders) (Box WP18)
      - Copy of partial draft with changes, 1985? (2 folders)
      - Draft with revisions, p. 370-381, 1985 Sept.
      - Draft, 1986, (3 folders)
      - Partial draft with Price's revisions, undated, (2 folders)
      - Galley excerpt, 1986 Apr.
      - Proofs with Price's corrections, 1986 (Box WP19)
      - Master proof, 1986
      - Jacket sketches from Ballantine Books (also Good Hearts), undated
      - Cover photograph, undated
      - Cover proofs, undated
      - Jacket, undated
      - First draft of a screenplay by Benedict Fitzgerald, 1987 June, (2 folders)
      - Screenplay by Benedict Fitzgerald, 1987 Oct.
    - The Laws of Ice (poetry, 1986) RESTRICTED (Box WP20)
      - The Aim, typescripts, undated
      - Ambrosia, typescripts, 1983 and undated
      - Before the Flood, typescript, 1984
      - Caught, typescript, undated
      - Caw, typescripts, undated
      - Cherokee, typescripts, 1982 and undated
      - The Claim, typescripts, 1984
      - Dead Man, Dying Girl, manuscript, typescripts, and proof, 1968, 1978, and undated, (2 folders)
      - Eels, typescript, undated
      - Epitaphs from the Greek Anthology, typescript, undated
      - For James Dean, typescript, undated
      - For Vivian Leigh, typescript, undated
      - Good Places, typescripts, 1983
      - Hawk Hill, typescripts, undated
      - The Heaven of Elizabeth Rodwell, My Mother, typescripts, 1983
      - His Discovery, typescript, 1984
      - House Snake, typescripts with revisions, 1983 and undated, (2 folders)
      - I Am Transmuting, manuscripts and typescript, 1968 and undated
      - Jonathan's Lament for David, typescript, undated
      - Last Conversation, typescript, 1983
      - A Life in Dreams, typescript, undated
      - Lighthouse, Mosquito Inlet, typescript, 1983
      - The Lines of Life, typescripts and proof, undated
      - The Lines of Life and The Sleeper in the Valley, proof from Shenandoah, 1966
      - Midnight, manuscripts and typescript, 1966-1968 and undated
      - Pears, typescript, undated
      - Porta Nigra, manuscripts and typescripts, 1966-1982 and undated
      - Rest, typescript, undated
      - Rincón 1, typescripts, 1982
      - Rincón 2, typescripts, 1982
      - Same Road, typescript, undated
      - Secret, typescript, undated
      - The Sleeper in the Valley, typescripts, 1960-1966 and undated
      - Three Visits, drafts and typescripts, 1985 and undated
      - A Tomb for Will Price, My Father, typescript, undated
      - Transatlantic, typescript, undated
      - Vision, typescript, 1984
      - Warm Springs, typescripts, 1982 and undated
      - Watchman, Tower, Midnight, manuscript and typescripts, 1986 and undated
      - What is Godly, typescripts, 1982 and undated
      - Typescript, undated, (2 folders)
      - Original copyedited typescript, 1986
      - Proof with Price's corrections, 1986
      - Cover photograph, undated
    - A Common Room (essays, 1987) RESTRICTED (Box WP21)
      - A Dim Warm Cave, typescripts and proof, 1983
      - A Fairly Crucial Choice, proofs, 1983
      - Family Stories: The Carters in Plains, manuscripts and typescript, 1976 and undated
      - Finding Work, manuscript and typescripts, 1967 Feb. 2 and undated
      - A Good Report, typescripts, 1982 Mar. 8-9
      - Heroes, manuscript, typescripts, and proof, 1978 Sept. 29-Oct. 19 and undated
      - Homeless. Home. manuscript and galley proof, 1977 Sept. 17-Nov. 26, (2 folders)
      - The Lonely Hunt for Power, manuscript and typescripts, 1973 Dec. 30 and undated
      - Love Across the Lines, draft, undated
      - Pantherine, Leonine, Orchidaceous, manuscripts and typescript, 1982 May 10-June 5 and undated